<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>Latest Posts Single Pane of Glass for Kubernetes Clusters with Clusterpedia For a while now, we have tools that promise that we can manage a fleet of Kubernetes clusters as one, yet they all failed to do just that. They all failed to provide a single pane of glass for all the clusters in a fleet. All the tools I know eventually show us what is happening in a single cluster and, honestly, I don’t need tools for that.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/kubernetes/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/kubernetes/index.html</guid>
      <description>Mastering Kubernetes: Dive into Workloads APIsYou might be new to Kubernetes or you might have been working with it for a while. No matter your experience level, you might not be aware of all the Kubernetes Workload APIs.&#xA;Mastering Kubernetes Testing Kyverno Chainsaw!Testing is important, no matter what you’re working on. If you write Java code, you need to test it. If you’re managing infrastructure, you need to test it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal Developer Platforms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/internal-developer-platforms/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/internal-developer-platforms/index.html</guid>
      <description>How Platform Engineering Compares to Running a RestaurantPlatform engineering should follow similar patterns as restaurants, yet we often confuse it with a kitchen or a supermarket.&#xA;Let me explain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/app-management/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/app-management/index.html</guid>
      <description>Exploring KCL: Configuration and Data Structure Language; CUE and Pkl Replacement?I’m in pain… and it’s self-inflicted… and I like it.&#xA;I tend to go through an endless number of tools, services, and format in search for better ways to do my job. I’m never satisfied. I always think that there is something better out there. So I go through pain of learning a new tool or a language only to jump into a new one shortly afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About The DeveOps Toolkit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</guid>
      <description>We want to help you learn the tools and the processes that you should be using and applying in your day-to-day job. We want to help you make decisions. What works well, what doesn’t work, why you should choose one tool over the other, and how to get up-to-speed quickly. Which tool works the best for a given task? What should we explore in more depth, and what is a waste of time?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor DevOps Toolkit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sponsor/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sponsor/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following sponsorship options are available on The DevOps Toolkit YouTube channel:&#xA;30-60 seconds ad inside a video Full video review and/or tutorial The objective behind accepting sponsorships in the The DevOps Toolkit channel is to cover the costs of equipment and post-production (e.g., editing, animations, etc.). As such, the number of sponsorship spots is limited.&#xA;30-60 seconds ad inside a video The price of a 30-60 seconds ad inside a video is $1000.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>