<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>Latest Posts Scaling Explained Through Kubernetes HPA, VPA, KEDA &amp; Cluster Autoscaler Scaling is probably one of the most important aspects of computing, and a common cause of bankrupcy.&#xA;If our processes use more memory and CPU than what they need, they are wasting money or “stealing” those resources from others thus making them less efficient. On the other hand,if we give processes less memory and CPU than what they need, their performance will be affected negatively making user experience suck.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/kubernetes/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/kubernetes/index.html</guid>
      <description>Scaling Explained Through Kubernetes HPA, VPA, KEDA &amp; Cluster AutoscalerScaling is probably one of the most important aspects of computing, and a common cause of bankrupcy.&#xA;If our processes use more memory and CPU than what they need, they are wasting money or “stealing” those resources from others thus making them less efficient. On the other hand,if we give processes less memory and CPU than what they need, their performance will be affected negatively making user experience suck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal Developer Platforms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/internal-developer-platforms/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/internal-developer-platforms/index.html</guid>
      <description>Mastering Developer Portals: Discover &amp; Integrate API Schemas with PortI am so dissaspointed with developer portal consoles for ignoring the fact that almost everything is discoverable through APIs. Why should I design forms and fields in Backstage if Backstage should be able to ask an API for a schema? Even if that schema is not exactly what I need and I might have to remove parts of it, that’s still easier and better than starting from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/app-management/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/app-management/index.html</guid>
      <description>Exploring KCL: Configuration and Data Structure Language; CUE and Pkl Replacement?I’m in pain… and it’s self-inflicted… and I like it.&#xA;I tend to go through an endless number of tools, services, and format in search for better ways to do my job. I’m never satisfied. I always think that there is something better out there. So I go through pain of learning a new tool or a language only to jump into a new one shortly afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development Environments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/development-environments/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/development-environments/index.html</guid>
      <description>Nix for Everyone: Unleash Devbox for Simplified DevelopmentNix is amazing, but also very difficult to manage. It assumes that you learned its programming language and that you are willing to ignore frastration generated by horrible documentation. I think it is one of the most useful projects out there that cannot be used by anyone but those willing to dedicate their lives to Nix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/security/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/security/index.html</guid>
      <description>How to Propagate Secrets Everywhere with External Secrets Operator (ESO) and CrossplaneToday I want to talk about secrets.&#xA;Don’t go away! I know that for many secrets is either boring or you think you already know everything there is to know about managing secrets. I will not talk about obvious “secret stuff”. Instead, I want to try to answer some less often asked yet important questions. “How do we make secrets easy and irrelevant to users?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CI/CD</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ci-cd/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ci-cd/index.html</guid>
      <description>If Dockerfile and Makefile Had a Baby... Earthly and EarthfileMakefile walks into a bar and notices Dockerfile sitting alone. She joins him, they talk, they flirt…&#xA;The rest of that story has been censored. You’ll have to fill in the gaps using your imagination.&#xA;…a baby was born, and that baby was named Earthfile.&#xA;Mastering Kubernetes Testing Kyverno Chainsaw!When I work locally, if I need to create a cluster I just execute cluster-create, wait for a few moments, and a local cluster with everything I need is running.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure-as-Code (IaC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/infrastructure-as-code/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/infrastructure-as-code/index.html</guid>
      <description>Terraform vs. Crossplane vs. Ansible - Rivals or Allies?I am often asked to compare Crossplane with Terraform, or Pulumi, or Ansible, or any other tool that primarily manages resources, be it those in hyperscalers like AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure, or in Kubernetes, or anywhere else. Well… Today I’m here to tell you that none of those tools are going away any time soon. We need all of those. We need configuration management tools like Ansible, we need Infrastructure-as-Code (IaC) tools like Terraform and Pulumi, and we need control planes, be it opinionated ones like AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure, or those that allow us to build our own control planes like Crossplane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Observability</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/observability/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/observability/index.html</guid>
      <description>Mastering Kubernetes Debugging: Leveraging eBPF with Inspektor GadgetKubernetes ecosystem is one of the most, if not the most extensive we’ve ever seen. There are tools for everything, including observability. We can collect metrics, logs, and traces for almost anything, we can query them, and we can see them in dashboards. There are hundreds of solutions for that alone, yet, sometimes, I miss simplicity of tools I would normally use in Linux.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebAssembly (WASM)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wasm/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wasm/index.html</guid>
      <description>Unleashing WebAssembly in Kubernetes with KwasmI am going to show you something you’ve seen many times before. Yet, looks can be deceiving. You will likely come to a wrong conclusion. What I will show is not what it might look like.&#xA;Here it goes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cloud/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cloud/index.html</guid>
      <description>Single Pane of Glass for Everything (AWS, Azure, GCP, Kubernetes, ...) with SteampipeRight now, I am connected to a PostgreSQL database and you are thinking that is boring. Who wants to see me querying a database?&#xA;Well… Wait until you see what I can query from such a database.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About The DeveOps Toolkit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/index.html</guid>
      <description>We want to help you learn the tools and the processes that you should be using and applying in your day-to-day job. We want to help you make decisions. What works well, what doesn’t work, why you should choose one tool over the other, and how to get up-to-speed quickly. Which tool works the best for a given task? What should we explore in more depth, and what is a waste of time?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sponsor DevOps Toolkit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/sponsor/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/sponsor/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following sponsorship options are available on The DevOps Toolkit YouTube channel:&#xA;30-60 seconds ad inside a video Full video review and/or tutorial The objective behind accepting sponsorships in the The DevOps Toolkit channel is to cover the costs of equipment and post-production (e.g., editing, animations, etc.). As such, the number of sponsorship spots is limited.&#xA;30-60 seconds ad inside a video The price of a 30-60 seconds ad inside a video is $1000.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>