<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Application Management</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/app-management/index.html</link>
    <description>Exploring KCL: Configuration and Data Structure Language; CUE and Pkl Replacement?I’m in pain… and it’s self-inflicted… and I like it.&#xA;I tend to go through an endless number of tools, services, and format in search for better ways to do my job. I’m never satisfied. I always think that there is something better out there. So I go through pain of learning a new tool or a language only to jump into a new one shortly afterwards.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/app-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring KCL: Configuration and Data Structure Language; CUE and Pkl Replacement?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/app-management/kcl/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/app-management/kcl/index.html</guid>
      <description>I’m in pain… and it’s self-inflicted… and I like it.&#xA;I tend to go through an endless number of tools, services, and format in search for better ways to do my job. I’m never satisfied. I always think that there is something better out there. So I go through pain of learning a new tool or a language only to jump into a new one shortly afterwards. Spending endless hours going through new stuff does not make sense, but I can’t help myself. Hopefully, I might save you from doing it yourself. That’s my goal. Go through the pain of trying out everything so that you don’t have to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Pkl the Ultimate Data Format? Unveiling the Challenger to YAML, JSON, and CUE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/app-management/pkl/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/app-management/pkl/index.html</guid>
      <description>Pkl is CUE killer!&#xA;Pkl is JSON and YAML killer!&#xA;Those are two sentences I heard lately. The former could be the case, while the latter is just silly. Let me explain.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>